http://www.theswami.com/pages/privacy.php

Privacy
This Website Privacy Policy addresses the kinds of information we may gather about you when you visit or submit forms or information on TheSwami.com Websites, how we expect to use that information, and the choices you have regarding our use of the information.  This Website Privacy Policy applies only to pages located at theswami.com and theswami.net (“Websites”).  At times, Websites may link to other content providers.  This Website Privacy Policy does not apply to any websites or content providers that you might visit by following links from our pages. We encourage you to review each third party website’s privacy policies before disclosing any information to that site.
TheSwami.com reserves the right to change this Website Privacy Policy at any time and for any reason, as permitted or required by applicable law, by posting changes to this page or a subsequent privacy page.
Users.
VISITORS: The Websites automatically log IP address information transmitted by your server, which may identify your or your Internet service provider’s Internet domain, but which normally would not include individually identifiable information such as your email address. You may browse free areas of our Websites without disclosing any additional information to us, although certain services and features may be unavailable unless you provide us additional information.
INFORMATION REQUESTERS: You may voluntarily choose to submit forms or information on our Websites or send us email to request newsletters, updates, information on our services, or to provide us with feedback. You should NOT send us any confidential information. Email and electronic forms are unsecured communication methods and TheSwami.com cannot guarantee that any such transmissions will remain confidential.  Except as follows, TheSwami.com will not release to any third party the content of such transmissions without your prior approval.  Your information may be incidentally accessible to third parties providing system administration, maintenance, or other services for our Websites, networks, servers, communications, or databases. However, we do not permit such third parties to use that information for other purposes.  In addition, TheSwami.com may provide your information to governmental agencies or other third parties as required by laws and regulations, including, for example, responding to subpoenas or other legal process.
REGISTERED USERS: In addition to those items and uses specified above, certain Personally Identifiable Information (“PII”) may be collected should you elect to register for access to the subscriber portion of the website.  This PII, including, but not limited to, name, address, telephone number and billing information, will be utilized by TheSwami.com to establish a login profile to identify registered users and to restrict access to the subscriber portions of the website to registered users.  In addition, TheSwami.com and the operators of the website may use this PII to assist in the evaluation of the website, its users and its performance.  If collected, PII will not be displayed or disclosed to any third parties for any purposes outside those mentioned above without your prior express written consent.  Other user submitted information, including data points and other user submitted data, which does not constitute protectable PII, may be used by TheSwami.com and the operators of the website for any purposes unless otherwise expressly restricted by these terms or the current statement of the Terms and Conditions of Use available online at TheSwami.com and TheSwami.net.
Use of Information.
We use visitor logs to monitor and improve the performance of TheSwami.com Websites, including navigation, links, search terms, and page and image load times.   If you choose to provide us with identifying information through a form, email, or via registration, we will use it to facilitate fulfillment of your requests and to improve the performance of the Websites. We may also store your identifying information, and may use that information for future communications from TheSwami.com to you, including the any Updates, Publications, announcements and other information which may be of interest to you, and any communication reasonably necessary to respond to and process your requests.   In the event you provide any information TheSwami.com may retain such information for an indefinite period to fulfill the requests, maintain records of delivered information, or conduct marketing activities.
Cookies.
The Websites may use "cookies" (small text files used to store information relating to visited Web pages) primarily to facilitate site navigation. If you are concerned about cookies, most Web browsers (such as Internet Explorer and Netscape) may be set to reject cookies or to prompt you individually to accept or reject a specific cookie. If your browser is not set to accept cookies, some pages may not display correctly and some features of the Websites may not be available to you.
Additional Information.
Additional information about TheSwami.com and the Websites, including additional information about this Privacy Policy, is available at users request.  For additional information, please contact support@theswami.com.
Login / Join
Login:
Password:
Not Registered?
Cart
Your cart is empty
(Recent Top Performers)
NFL Last 4 WeeksMoney Makers (Jimmy Rogers)11-2 (+88.00)Predictable Patterns9-2 (+68.00)Big Play Power Consensus8-2 (+56.00)NCAA FB Last 4 WeeksUmpire's Call5-0 (+50.00)Money Makers (Jimmy Rogers)12-1 (+109.00)The Insiders5-1 (+39.00)NCAA BKB Last 2 WeeksThe Insiders7-0 (+70.00)Coaches'
Consensus12-1 (+101.00)The Call10-1 (+89.00)
